(Amy:)Okay, okay, this is obviously
very important to her.
(Amy:)Let's just, we'll help her study
so she can get done quicker.
(Leonard:)Here...
here, I'm gonna quiz you.
(Amy:)I'm gonna quiz you.
I got your notes!
If you want these,
(Amy:)they're gonna be
at the strip club!
(Bernadette:)Aren't you gonna chase her?
(Penny:)To the walk-in closet? Sure.
(Leonard:)Okay, so we agree,
(Leonard:)whenever someone
takes us off topic
(Leonard:)they get their arm
hair yanked off.
(Raj:)And I really
can't let that happen
(Raj:)or the girl who does
my eyebrows will think
(Raj:)I've been cheating on her.
(Leonard:)All right, now, one benefit
of quantum coupling...
Wait, no, question:
(Sheldon:)who decides if someone's
gone off topic?
(Leonard:)I think it'll be pretty clear.
If not, we'll take a vote.
(Leonard:)Oh, and also...
Ow!